<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Anarchy Linux</title>
    <link>https://anarchylinux.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Anarchy Linux</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2019 20:53:22 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://anarchylinux.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Features</title>
      <link>https://anarchylinux.org/features/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anarchylinux.org/features/</guid>
      <description>The Anarchy Linux installers offers a few pretty amazing features, including the following:
Large selection of kernels  base or base-devel system installation default linux kernel hardened linux kernel LTS (Long Term Support) linux kernel zen linux kernel  Multiple partitioning methods  Automatic partitioning (optional swap) Automatic LUKS-encrypted partitioning on LVM (optional encrypted swap) Manual partitioning  A whole bunch of optional DEs and WMs (Desktop Environments and Window Managers)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Screenshots</title>
      <link>https://anarchylinux.org/screenshots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anarchylinux.org/screenshots/</guid>
      <description>Coming soon &amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Telegram group</title>
      <link>https://anarchylinux.org/posts/tg_group/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2019 20:53:22 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anarchylinux.org/posts/tg_group/</guid>
      <description>We started a Telegram group I&amp;rsquo;m announcing the creation of a discussion group in the Telegram instant messaging service.
We invite you to join the group by clicking on this link to discuss new ideas and features to be implemented in future releases.
Together we can make Anarchy more than just an installer!
We&amp;rsquo;re hoping to see you soon!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release v1.0.5</title>
      <link>https://anarchylinux.org/posts/release-105/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 10:02:34 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anarchylinux.org/posts/release-105/</guid>
      <description>Another Anarchy update, yay!
1.0.5&amp;rsquo;s changelog is actually quite long, despite being a &amp;ldquo;patch&amp;rdquo; version.
You can check out the changelog on our release page for a summary or continue reading for a more in-depth look into the changes.
Firstly we&amp;rsquo;ve completely removed the GUI installer, since it was very outdated and it hasn&amp;rsquo;t been built since like v1.0.0. AFAIK nobody has complained about the lack of GUI builds, but if enough people would like it back, it can be arranged, although we&amp;rsquo;d need some maintainers for it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We&#39;d like your feedback</title>
      <link>https://anarchylinux.org/posts/feedback/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2019 10:25:41 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anarchylinux.org/posts/feedback/</guid>
      <description>Hello,
My name is Erazem and I&amp;rsquo;m a fairly new contributor to the Anarchy Linux project and the author of this website.
Like (hopefully) most of you reading this, I really like the project and as a beginner in open source I wanted to contribute to it. Since I only know a bit about bash scripting I haven&amp;rsquo;t been able to contribute much actual code yet, but that didn&amp;rsquo;t stop me from contributing altogether.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release 1.0.4</title>
      <link>https://anarchylinux.org/posts/release-104/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 10:25:41 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anarchylinux.org/posts/release-104/</guid>
      <description> On June 8, 2019, Anarchy Linux received its 1.0.4 release, finally. With the upcoming release of 1.0.5, which already has way more changes, we can safely say this was a minor release,
Changelog:  QT4 was removed from the package list MongoDB was removed from the optional software list A timeout was added to the syslinux config file arch-wiki-cli was removed from the package list  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Website</title>
      <link>https://anarchylinux.org/posts/new-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 09:25:41 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://anarchylinux.org/posts/new-website/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;ve stumbled upon our revamped website. It was built to be modern and fast using the Hugo static website generator and the Terrassa theme.
If you haven&amp;rsquo;t already, check out our Github project page.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>